<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DIGITA 25</title>
    <link>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DIGITA 25</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accepted Papers</title>
      <link>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/accepted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/accepted/</guid>
      <description>Accepted Papers Once the peer-review process is finalized, we will announced here the accepted submissions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dates</title>
      <link>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/dates/</guid>
      <description>Dates Paper submission deadline: November 17th, 2024 Paper notification: January 8th, 2025 Camera Ready Deadline: February 2nd, 2025 Workshop: to be announced </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organization</title>
      <link>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/organization/</guid>
      <description>Committees Organizing Committee Sara Montagna, Department of Pure and Applied Science - University of Urbino Carlo Bo, Italy Marco Picone, Department of Sciences and Methods for Engineering (DISMI) - University of Modena and Reggio Emilia Samuele Burattini, Department of Computer Science and Engineering - Alma Mater Studiorum University of Bologna, Italy Program Committee Gianluca Aguzzi, University of Bologna, Italy Claudia Campolo, University Mediterranea of Reggio Calabria, Italy Rem Collier, University College Dublin, Dublin, Ireland Angelo Croatti, ASL Romagna, Italy Lukas Esterle, Aarhus University, Denmark Mirgita Frasheri, Aarhus University, Denmark Stefano Mariani, University of Modena and Reggio Emilia, Italy Alessandro Ricci, University of Bologna, Italy &amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Previous Events</title>
      <link>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/previous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/previous/</guid>
      <description>Previous Events Despite changing the name, this workshop represents the second edition of the MADTECC (Medical Applications with Digital Twins and Edge-Cloud Continuum) workshop, following its debut at PerCom 2024. This year, we aim to broaden the scope of the topics, keeping the spirit of involving researchers working in practical applications of Digital Twins to complex ecosystems without the constraints on the specific domain of healthcare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/program/</guid>
      <description>Program Updates on the workshop program will be posted here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for papers</title>
      <link>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://digita-percom.github.io/2025/cfp/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers The Digital Twin Ecosystems &amp;amp; Applications (DIGITA) workshop aims to provide a platform for sharing knowledge and experiences in the field of Digital Twin Ecosystems and their practical applications. This workshop seeks to explore the latest trends, challenges, and opportunities in the engineering and application of pervasive systems adopting the Digital Twin Ecosystems approach. Methodologies and tools for design and development, enabling technologies, and innovative use cases will be presented and discussed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
